本:嗨,妈妈,嗨,爸爸,你们还好么?
Ben: Hi mum, hi dad.How are you guys?
麦琪:嗨,宝贝,我们很好.
Maggie: Hi honey.We're fine.
杰森:今天上学怎么样?本?
Jason: How's school today Ben?
本:太棒了!
Ben: Fantastic!
杰森:哦!那很好呃?
Jason: Ooh!That good huh?
本:在这儿等你.今天早上,校长公布完平均分之后,被电击了一下,当她拿着麦克风的时候,她说了一句非常难听的话.
Ben: Wait til you here.This morning when the principle was finished doing announcements over
the PA, she got a shock when she touched the microphone, and yelled out a
real naughty word
麦琪:所以,这就是你所谓的太棒的一天?
Maggie: So that's what made it a fantastic day?
本:你说的没错.你能听到那句脏话在会堂里回响.
Ben: You bet.Boy, you could hear that dirty word echoing through the halls.
杰森:好了,听着,还有谁熬过了又一个上学的日子?
Jason: Well, look who made it through another day of school.
迈克:差点没熬过去,嗨,
Mike: Well barely.Hey, uh dad.
爸爸.我可不可以向您借217块钱?
Do you think I could borrow about two hundred and seventeen dollars?
好的,5点钟我会去睡觉.
Ok, I'll settle for five.
广播:美国西部时间,现在4:14分,是歌曲有奖竞猜时间,2000美金,您只需要拔打555100,告诉我这首歌曲的名称……
Radio: WZLB time, it's four fifteen and that's Jack pot call in time.Two thousand
big ones in a hopper right now, just waiting for you to call five five
five loot, and tell me the name of this song
迈克:我知道!我知道!我知道这歌的名字,本!!我猜着了!我猜着了!
Mike: I knew it!I knew it!I knew the song Ben!I got it!I got it!
本:已经有人打过了.
Ben: Dial already.
杰森和麦琪:去,迈克,去,赶快!
Jason: and Maggie: Go Mike go.Hurry up!
迈克:知道么,以前开萝尔一直放这歌,我都快烦死了.
Mike: You know Carol's been driving me crazy playing that song.
天,有她做我妹妹,我太高兴了.
Boy am I glad she's my sister.
杰森:啊,难道那个不对么?
Jason: Ah, doesn't that get right here?
迈克:嗨,我知道那歌,它是……啊是语音提示,所有的都占线.
Mike: Hi, I knew that song, it's...Ah it's a recording.All lines are busy.
麦琪:啊,好可惜啊,迈克.好了,下回吧.
Maggie: Ah what a shame Mike.Well maybe next time.
迈克:嗨,爸爸 ,鉴于我刚才没赢回来那2000块,那5怎么样?
Mike: Yeah, hey dad, since I didn't win the two thousand, how about the five?
杰森:今天不是你的幸运日,迈克.
Jason: This isn't your day Mike.
本:我得到了一些消息,听了你肯定会高兴起来的,迈克.等,只到你听到宾夕法尼亚州的坎小姐是怎么说的.
Ben: I got some news that will cheer you up Mike.Wait til you hear
what Miss Cunn said over the Pa
杰森:量你们也不敢引用她的话.
Jason: Don't you dare quote her.
开萝尔:嗨,妈妈,嗨,爸爸.
Carol: Hey mum, hey dad
麦琪:嗨,宝贝.
Maggie: Hi sweetheart.
杰森:开萝尔,有几分常态了.
Jason: Carol, a breath of normalcy.
开萝尔:哦,听着,下周野营活动,
Carol: Oh listen.I need a note form one of you for the field trip next
我需要你们中间有一个写个批条,还需要些罐装的食物,施舍用.
week.I need some canned food for the charity drive.
杰森和麦琪:太棒了.
Jason: and Maggie: Great.
开萝尔:我真的是需要给鼻子动个手术.
Carol: And I really need a nose job.
麦琪:没问题.刚才她是不是说了……
Maggie: Sure.Did she just say...
杰森:对.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:还有,我说了……
Maggie: And I said..
杰森:对.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:不.
Maggie: No.
杰森:对.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:开萝尔!
Maggie: Carol!
杰森:开萝尔!
Jason: Carol!
麦琪:开萝尔.
Maggie: Carol.
开萝尔:干么.
Carol: Yes
麦琪:你刚才是不是说……
Maggie: Did you just say...
杰森:宝贝,什么东西,这个……?
Jason: Honey, what's this..?
麦琪:您先走.
Maggie: After you.
杰森:亲爱的,这是什么东西?
Jason: Honey what's this..
麦琪:你刚才是不是说……
Maggie: Did you just say..
杰森:我放弃.
Jason: I give up.
麦琪:刚才你是不是说你想对鼻子做个手术?
Maggie: Did you just say you wanted a nose job?
开萝尔:我就知道你们会不高兴的.
Carol: I knew you guys would be upset.
杰森:我们没有不高兴.
Jason: We're not upset.
麦琪:怎么会呢.
Maggie: Of course not.
杰森:肯定高兴.我们只是想了解一下,事情的原委.
Jason: No.We just want to know what this is all about.
麦琪:我们绝对没有不高兴的意思.
Maggie: But we are certainly not upset.
杰森:如果你刚才要当真的话,我们就会不高兴.
Jason: We'd be upset if you were serious about this.
开萝尔:我当真的.
Carol: I am.
麦琪:那,好吧,我们不高兴.
Maggie: Well then.We're upset.
开萝尔:妈妈,我一直在想这件事,
Carol: Mum.I've been thinking about this for a long time.
很长时间了.就在上周,
And then last week, this girl in my Latin class came in after having it done,
跟我上拉丁语课的女孩在做完手术之后回来上课了,,妈妈她看起来棒极了.
and mum she looks great.
麦琪:可是,宝贝,你的鼻子挺可爱啊,你有一个翘翘的小纽扣鼻.
Maggie: But honey you have a cute nose.You have a perky little button nose.
杰森:没错,你的鼻子跟你妈妈的一样.
Jason: Yeah, you have your mother's nose.
杰森:我知道,不,
Carol: I know.No mum mum.It looks good on you.
妈妈妈妈.长在你脸上很好看,
You can get away with a big nose.
你鼻子大点也没事儿,因为你其它部位也很大.
I mean, cos all your other features are big too.
不是"大",我的意思是说……
I don't mean big, I just mean...
杰森:开萝尔,放弃吧.
Jason: Carol, just give up.
麦琪:开萝尔,谁说你长了个大鼻子了?
Maggie: Carol, who says you have a big nose?
开萝尔:我本来就长了个大鼻子,这就是问题所在,不是么?
Carol: Well I do and that's what matters, right?
迈克:嗨,开萝尔,有个叫夏洛特*鲍热尔正在线上.
Mike: Hey Carol, someone named Charlotte Bowzer's on the phone.
开萝尔:哦,太好了!她会告诉我关于她手术的所有情况.
Carol: Oh great!She's giving me all the information about her plastic surgeon.
杰森:开萝尔,我们在跟你说话呢.
Jason: Carol.We're talking to you.
开萝尔:我知道,得是这个很重要.
Carol: I know, but this is important.
迈克:等,等等一会儿.
Mike: Wait, wait wait a minute.Did I hear right.
刚才我没听错吧?开萝尔想做个美容手术?
I Carol actually considering plastic surgery?
杰森:迈克,你操什么心.
Jason: Mike, this doesn't concern you.
迈克:得,不过,在我走之前,还想说一句……太妙了.
Mike: Right, but before I go, I just wanted to say ..Bravo.
杰森:这不像是开萝尔的做风,她从哪儿学来的这些对自己的长相这么的关注?
Jason: This isn't like Carol.
麦琪?
I mean where did she get this hyper concern for her looks?Maggie?
麦琪:我的鼻子有什么问题么?
Maggie: What's wrong with my nose?
杰森:你的鼻子实在是太漂亮了.让我最初一见钟情的就是你的鼻子.
Jason: Your nose is beautiful.
实际上,当你浮现在我心目中的时候,
Your nose is the first part of you I fell in love with.
我看到的只有这两个鼻孔.看,
In fact when I get a picture of you in my mind,
就鼻子本身而言,
all I see are those two come hither nostrils.Yeah look at this.
简直完美.上帝的鼻子就应该是这个样子,
As far as noses go, this is perfection.God should have such a nose.
我在说什么?这是上帝的鼻子.
What am I saying?This is the nose of god.
麦琪:杰森,就算是你在开萝尔那儿受了打击,
Maggie: Jason, just because you are frustrated with Carol,
也不应该把它撒在我身上.
doesn't mean you have to take it out on me.
杰森:哦,我没有受什么打击,
Jason: Oh, I'm not frustrated, I'm just confused.
我只是纳闷.
I mean why would our sensible Carol want to get her face rearranged,
为什么我们的开萝尔会想把自己的那张脸重新给安排一下,就是因为某个叫夏洛特*鲍热尔的么?
just because someone named Charlotte Bowzer did it?
本:嗨嗨.开萝尔想把自己的脸给重新移植,这是不是真的?
Ben: Hey hey.Is it true that Carols getting a face transplant?
杰森:本,我来给你点忠告,
Jason: Ben, let me give you some advice.Don't listen to Mike.
别听迈克瞎说.不仅这件事情上应该如此,而且总体上生活中也应该如此.
That applies not only to this case, but to life in general.
麦琪:杰森,你知道是什么原因么,
Maggie: Jason, you know what.This nose thing is just a phase.
给鼻子动手术只是一个阶段性的问题,很多少女都有过这经历.我知道这很难以置信,
I mean a lot of teenage girls go through it.
但即使是我,也有过那种想法.
And I know it's hard to believe, but even I did.
杰森:我相信.
Jason: I believe it.
麦琪:你真相信?
Maggie: You do?
杰森:在克服了重重困难之后.你说得对,
Jason: I mean with great difficulty.You are right.
这是个阶段性的问题,我知道该怎么对待这件事情了.
This is a phase and I know just what to do about it.
我们让她坐下来,跟她交谈,寻问她这么做的理由.
We sit her down, we talk to her and we ask her reasons.
如此这般,我们就会有一个充满智慧之光的对话,
Then we have an intelligent dialogue between a responsible child and her
对话的一方是懂事的孩子,而另一方是她的父母---坚实的后盾.
supportive parents.
麦琪:没错,我们会向她提起所有应该考虑的问题,
Maggie: Sure.We ask her all the right questions and Carol will see that
而后,开萝尔会明白自己对这件事情还没有考虑周全.
she hasn't thought this thing through at all.
开萝尔:修鼻术,又称鼻部整形手术,无须住院,通常只需局部麻醉,4小时后药力消退.通常建议病人再卧床一天.手术后会因为肿胀等出现鼻部及眼部周围青紫.整个手术只需要2400美元.
Carol: A nose job or rhyno plasti is an out patient procedure normally involving a local anesthetic that wears off in about four hours.It is usually recommended that the
patient remain in bed for one additional day.
There is discoloration of the nose and
orbits of the eyes as a result of haemotoma from blows to the mallet.And
it costs only twenty four hundred dollars
麦琪:之前我说了些什么?她根本没有对此考虑清楚.
Maggie: what did I say?She hasn't thought this through at all.
开萝尔:首先,我还是从前的那个开萝尔,
Carol: First of all,
各门功课全优,所有事情都会有周详的考虑.至于手术,
I'm still the same Carol who gets straight A's and thinks everything through.
这不是一时兴起头脑发热,也不是你们所想的什么青春期综合症.
And this is not a whim or an adolescent phase if that's what you're thinking.
杰森:哦,我可没那么想.
Jason: Oh not me.
开萝尔:这儿基本的问题是,你认为一个人鼻子的大小会影响他的生活道路么?
Carol: The basic question here is,
do you believe that the size of a persons nose can affect the course of
their life?
杰森:那……
Jason: Well..
开萝尔:解释解释卡尔?
Carol: Explain Carl Molden?
杰森:咱们先不要提卡尔,好么.
Jason: Let's keep the size of Carl Moldens honker out of this, ok.
我们想知道你为什么想做这个手术.
We want to find out why you want this surgery.
开萝尔:我会对自己的相貌更自信,而且,
Carol: Well I'd feel better about the way I looked, and well,
我会对自己更自信.
I'd feel better about myself.
杰森:好了,宝贝,你的相貌并没有什么问题.
Jason: Well honey, there's nothing wrong with the way you look.
开萝尔:爸爸,你忘了你努力减胖的时候了么?
Carol: Dad.Remember when you started working out with weights?
杰森:没有.
Jason: Yeah.
开萝尔:还有妈妈,记得你为什么染发么?
Carol: And mum, remember why started coloring your hair?
麦琪:我有时得出镜.
Maggie: I add occasional high lights.
开萝尔:但是,
Carol: But don't you see.
你们自己没发现么,你们做这些就是为了让自己对自己的外观更自信.
You guys did those things so you'd feel better about the way you look.
而这也正是我想要的.
That's all I'm asking.
杰森:好了,你妈妈和我得商量商量这事,
Jason: Alright, well your mother and I have to discuss this,
能不能请你先离开这个房间?
so would you mind stepping out of the room?
开萝尔;没问题,没问题.
Carol: Sure, sure.
杰森:你能不能再离开的远一点?
Jason: Could you step a little further out?
开萝尔:哦,没问题,没问题.
Carol: Oh fine.Fine.
麦琪:杰森 ,这太敏感了,
Maggie: Jason, this discussion is a great touch because Carol will actually
因为开萝尔会认为我们在拒绝她之前就已经商量好了.
think that we considered this before we said no.
杰森:啊……
Jason: Well...
麦琪:不用"啊",我知道,我太明白那"啊"了.
Maggie: Don't say well I know.I know that well too well.
杰森:啊,宝贝,
Jason: Well honey I don't want this any more than you do,
我和你一样,也不想要这样,不过我们一直都相信开萝尔自己的判断能力.
but we've always relied on Carols common sense.
麦琪:这种判断能力先得经过我们批准.
Maggie: Which she has taken leave of.
杰森:突然之间,开始像对待本那样的小孩那样对她,说不通的.
Jason: No point to suddenly start treating her like she's Ben's age.
麦琪:那,她会习惯的.
Maggie: Well she'll get used to it.
杰森:我们应该去告诉她可以做这个鼻子整形手术.
Jason: I say we should go ahead and tell her she can have the nose job.
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:如果她自己掏腰包的话.这样一来,
Jason: If she pays for it herself.
每一个子儿她都得存起来,要相当长时间,
See that way, for every dime she has to save,
这样她就会有时间考虑那样是不是值得.2400美元.
she'll have time to see if it's worth it.Twenty four hundred dollars.
且得掂量着呢,麦琪.
That's a lot of thinking Maggie.
麦琪:可是,亲爱的,如果她攒下了那笔钱,而她还是想要手术,那可怎么办?
Maggie: But honey.What if she saves the money and she still wants a nose job?
杰森:等到开萝尔攒足2400美金的时候,她就会想要一个脸部整形术了.
Jason: By the time Carol saves twenty four hundred dollars, she's going to need a face life.
开萝尔:一周十块,2400块要224除以52……4年半.嗨,迈克,借你点银子.
Carol: Ten dollars a week into twenty four hundred is two hundred and twenty four, divided by fifty two is ...four and a half years.Hello Michael.Hot shirt
迈克:不,开萝尔,
Mike: No Carol.I don't have any money to lend you.
我没有余钱借给你.知道为什么么,
And you know what, it really pains me to say that,
我确实很难启齿说那个不字,看看这是多值得你去付出的.
knowing what a worthy cause this is.
开萝尔:噢,你这讨厌的家伙.
Carol: Oh go squeeze some zits.
迈克:说这话多粗鲁啊,
Mike: Now what a rude thing to say,
尤其是对我这样一个人,
especially to a guy who happens to know of a job where you could make
我刚巧还真知道你从哪儿能挣大钱.
some big money.
开萝尔:什么工作?
Carol: What job?
迈克:不不不不,太迟了,你伤了我了.
Mike: No no no no.It's too late Carol.I'm hurt.
开萝尔:哦,好了吧,迈克,对不起.什么工作?
Carol: Oh come on Mike.I'm sorry.What job?
迈克:真的对不起?
Mike: Truly sorry?
开萝尔:痛哭流泣.什么工作?
Carol: In tears.What's the job?
迈克:那好,这就是美国运通需要某个人能取代卡尔.
Mike: Well, word is, American express need someone to replace Carl Molden.
迈克:你这混蛋.
Carol: You scum.
迈克:好了好了,只不过是个小小的玩笑.现在,
Mike: Alright alright.So it's a little joke.I was just kidding there.
说正经的,开萝尔.
Ok, alright lets be serious now Carol.Ok, now come on Carol.
好了,开萝尔.你没必要把所有的钱都花在手术上.
You don't need to spend all that money on a nose job.
开萝尔:因为我已经很漂亮了,是么?
Carol: Right, because I'm beautiful already?
迈克:别这样,我说过了不开玩笑.
Mike: No I said let's be serious.
这样的,我知道到哪儿你可以半价做整鼻手术.
Now look, I know where you can get a nose job for half the price.
开萝尔:哇!
Carol: Wow!
迈克:急成这样了!
Mike: Igor!
本:对我而言很好.
Ben: It is good with me.
杰森:晚饭!
Jason: Dinner!
本:哦,天,哦,天,哦,天!肝儿,啊----!
Ben: Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy!Liver ahhhhh!
麦琪:肝对你有好处.
Maggie: liver is good for you.
迈克:哦,我闻到的那是肝儿么?
Mike: Oh is that liver I smell?
麦琪:对,含有丰富的铁.
Maggie: Yes, and its got lots of iron in it.
迈克:妈妈,我们难道不能吃一小点儿么?
Mike: Mum, can't we just eat a skeleton instead?
麦琪:怎么会事?
Maggie: What in the world?
开萝尔:鉴于我需要花费这么长的时间攒钱,
Carol: Since I have to wait so long to save the money I need,
我已经决定巧妙使化妆品来修饰我面部的某些美中不足.
I decided to camouflage my facial deformity, with the subtle use of make up.
迈克:好美啊,开萝尔.
Mike: Looking good Carol.
麦琪:够了,开萝尔.现在上楼去,洗掉.
Maggie: That's enough Carol.Upstairs right now and wash it off.
开萝尔:可是,妈妈!
Carol: But mum!
杰森:这不管用的,开萝尔,你还得继续自己攒钱.
Jason: It's not going to work Carol, you are still going to have to save
the money yourself
开萝尔:好的,没问题.
Carol: Alright fine.Fine.
我上楼,回我房间,
I'll go up to my room,
不过我想让你们知道,我再也不回来了.听好了?
but I just want you to know I am never coming out.Ok?
好好想想.永不.
Just think about it.Never.
杰森:你到底在干什么?
Jason: Now exactly what are you doing?
迈克:被强制回到房间,没有晚餐.
Mike: Being sent to my room without dinner.
杰森:你已经吃了双份儿的.
Jason: You're getting a double portion.
迈克:不不,爸爸.
Mike: No no dad.
杰森:还有你.
Jason: And you too.
本:嗨!
Ben: Hey!
广播:好了,现在是有奖歌曲竞猜时间.
Radio: Alright its jack pot call-in time.
迈克:这次我不会错过的.
Mike: I'm not missing it this time.
广播:我们已经追加了1000美元,
Radio: We've put another one thousand dollars into the jack pot for the
奖给猜中歌曲的第五位听众.
fifth caller to identify our mystery song.
迈克:我知道了.嗨,还是同一首歌.开萝尔,
Mike: I got it.Hey it's the same song.I got this one.
开萝尔,把电话给我.给我,
Carol, Carol, get off the phone right now.Off now.I don't believe this.
现在.真是不敢相信,我知道这歌的名字,可是开萝尔不让我用电话.
I know the name of this song and Carols not letting me use the phone.
广播:现在这是我们打进电话的第五位听众.嗨,你的答案是什么?
Radio: And here's our fifth caller right now.Hi what's your answer?
开萝尔:以爱的名义.
Carol: In the name of love.
广播:太对了.你的名字呢,亲爱的?
Radio: That is absolutely right.What's your name honey?
开萝尔:开萝尔*希佛.
Carol: Carol Seaver.
麦琪和杰森:什么!
Maggie and Jason: What!
广播:你已经赢得了3000美元.你准备怎么花这些钱,有什么计划么?
Radio: You just won three thousand dollars.Do you know what you are going to
do with all that money
开萝尔:当然有.
Carol: I sure do.
麦琪:亲爱的,我们不允许你这么做,是为了你好.
Maggie: Honey, we're saying no for your own good.
本:为她本人好,扯到这上来了.
Ben: Speaking of her own good..
开萝尔:这怎么可能是为了我自己好?
Carol: How could this possibly be for my own good?
杰森:开萝尔,我们年龄比你大些,
Jason: Carol, we're a little older, a little wiser.
经验比你多点.我们看得更透.
We have some more perspective.
开萝尔:你们违背自己神圣的誓约,是为我好!
Carol: Breaking your solemn promise is for my own good!
杰森:有时候呢父母背弃自己的承诺也是迫不得已.
Jason: Well sometimes parents just have to be unfair.
开萝尔:我会记住这一天的,我的父亲母亲最初信誓旦旦,
Carol: I'm going to remember this day.
而后背信弃义.
The day my parents gave me their word and then broke it.
迈克:我饱了.
Mike: Boy am I full.
本:肝比我想像的要好.
Ben: Yeah, liver wasn't as bad as I thought.
迈克:对,我就是忍不住还要吃那东西,可以原谅我们么?
Mike: Yeah.I just couldn't stop eating that stuff mum.Can we be excused?
麦琪:好的.杰森!
Maggie: Ok.Jason!
杰森:我刚才在想.我们已经阻止了开萝尔,
Jason: I was just thinking.I know we've stopped Carol, but at what price?
但是代价呢?
Now we'll never know why she's so upset about the way she looks.
现在,我们永远不可能知道她为什么对自己的相貌那么失望.
Maybe she'll never know.What's causing this negative self image?
也许她也不知道.
I just can't help but feel we are cutting off our own nose to spite our
引发这种消极的自我形象的原因是什么?我禁不住想我们是割掉了自己的鼻子反过来怨恨我们的脸.
face.Ok, bad choice of words.
开萝尔:迈克.
Carol: Mike.
迈克:好,布鲁克,你赢了.
Mike: Ok Brooke.You win.
开萝尔:得了,迈克,起来.
Carol: Come on Mike.Get up.
迈克:布鲁克,哦,开萝尔,怎么回事?
Mike: Brooke.Oh Carol, no what's going on.
开萝尔:迈克,我需要你的帮助.
Carol: Mike I need your help.
迈克:开萝尔迷失方向了.
Mike: Carol get lost.
开萝尔:给你50块钱.
Carol: It's worth fifty bucks.
迈克:好吧,说吧.
Mike: Alright, name it.
开萝尔:开车送我去个任何人都不知道的地方.
Carol: I need you to drive me somewhere without anybody knowing.
迈克:哪儿?
Mike: Where?
开萝尔:有什么不一样么?
Carol: What difference does it make?
迈克:大不一样,开萝尔.我不想让我的朋友看见我开车跟你在一起.
Mike: A lot Carol.I don't want my friends seeing me driving you around.
开萝尔:那好,那你开车送我到城里的医师事务所.
Carol: Alright, I need you to drive me to the doctors building downtown.
迈克:医师事务所?
Mike: The doctors building?
开萝尔:对,别担心,那儿你不会撞见我的任何朋友的.她们从来不就医.
Carol: Yeah, don't worry.You won't ruin into any of your friends there.They are beyond medicine.
迈克:嗨,开萝尔,你真的要做鼻子整形么?
Mike: Hey Carol.Are you really going through with this nose thing?
开萝尔:关你什么事.
Carol: It's none of your business.
迈克:嗨,开萝尔,
Mike: Hey Carol, you know that doctor is not going to do anything without
你知道,没有病人的同意,医生是不会做任何事情的.
parents consent.
开萝尔:让爸爸,妈妈签字也许根本不是难事.
Carol: Maybe getting mum and dad to sign a consent form isn't so hard at all.
迈克:伪造.
Mike: Forgery.
开萝尔:嘘.
Carol: Shhh
迈克:我从前不知道你也会如此狡猾.你还行.
Mike: You know, I had no idea you could be so slimy.You're ok.
好的,刚才说到哪儿了.
Ok, now where was I.
开萝尔和迈克:不!
Carol and Mike: No!
迈克:其实,你刚才没必要过来的.
Carol: You know, you didn't have to come up here.
迈克:对,刚才我就是不想待在车里.你想让我走么?
Mike: Yeah, I just didn't want to wait in the car.You want me to leave?
开萝尔:只要你在这儿……
Carol: Well as long as you are here...
接待员:姓名?
Receptionist: Name?
开萝尔:嗨,我和科瓦拜什大夫约过了,
Carol: Hi.I have an appointment with Doctor Kowabash for a preliminary
鼻部整形术的初步诊断.
consultation for rhyno plasti.I have the parents consent form right here.
我这儿有家长的同意表.我父亲的签名,
See, my parent's signature, my father's signature.
我会让他们在手术之前现金支付,
I'll have them pay in cash before the procedure,
那我现在就过去那边等你叫我.谢谢你.
so I'll just wait there until you call me.Thank you.
接待员:姓名.
Receptionist: Name.
开萝尔:对,我有多傻啊,对不起.我看到医生真的是有些紧张,
Carol: Yes, how silly of me.I'm so sorry.I get really nervous around doctors.
不只是医生还有接待员,实际上只要人家穿白衣服,我就紧张.
And receptionists.Anyone in white actually.
接待员:姓名.
Receptionist: Name.
迈克:哦,开萝尔*希佛.
Mike: Oh it's Carol Seaver.
接待员:她的姓名.
Receptionist: Her name.
迈克:就是她的名字.
Mike: It is.
接待员:哦.
Receptionist: Oh.
开萝尔:他是一个非常有名的精神病大夫.
Carol: He's a well respected psychiatrist.
接待员:他?
Receptionist: Him?
开萝尔:没是他,他就是我哥哥,傻子似的.
Carol: Not him.He's my stupid brother.
接待员:谢谢.
Receptionist: Thank you.
迈克:很顺利.
Mike: Smooth.
接待员:对,你有杰森*希佛医生的电话么?
Receptionist: Yes, do you have a listing for a doctor Jason Seaver?
(电话响起)
(phone rings)
本:好好.你好,希佛大夫不是跟精神障碍患者看病,就是在厕所.爸爸!爸爸!
Ben: Ok ok.Hello.Doctor Seaver is either with a mental patient, or in the
bathroom.Dad!Dad
杰森:本,你知道规矩的.我跟病人看病的时候不许打扰.
Jason: Ben, you know the rules.You don't interrupt when I'm with a patient.
本:精神病人.
Ben: Mental patient.
麦琪:嗨,亲爱的.
Maggie: Hi honey.
本:你要和我妈妈谈么?你不用这么客气.妈妈.
Ben: You want to talk to my mum?You're welcome very much.Mum.
麦琪:谢谢.你好,对,开萝尔是我女儿.
Maggie: Thanks.Hello.Yes Carol's my daughter.She's there.Where's there?
她在你们那儿,地方在哪儿?对不起,哪位是科瓦拜什大夫?
Excuse me.Who is doctor Kalibash?What?
什么?不,我们肯定没有签字.不不,
No we certainly did not sign a consent form.
请什么也不要告诉她.我们马上过去.谢谢你.杰森!
No no, please don't say a word to her.We'll be right down.Thank you.Jason!
本:他在跟精神病人看病.
Ben: He's with a mental patient.
麦琪:真不敢相信.
Maggie: I can not believe this.
迈克:一些人真的是有意识对自己做那个,
Mike: Can you believe that some people actually do that to themselves
你会相信么?
on purpose?Oh sorry.
开萝尔:迈克,如果你想说那样的事情,就去车上等着,好么?
Carol: Mike, if you're going to say stuff like that, wait in the car.Ok?
迈克:对不起,我只是想说看起来很痛苦.
Mike: I'm sorry.I just meant that it looks like major pain.
开萝尔:迈克.
Carol: Mike.
迈克:哦,好了.听着!
Mike: Oh right.Look!
开萝尔,如果你小肚鸡肠这话都受不了,那你为什么还要去做了?
Carol, if you are so chicken about this, why are you even doing this?
开萝尔:我为什么做手术,你心里非常明白.
Carol: You know very well why I'm doing this.
你就是想刺激我,又是你的一个小把戏.
You are just setting me up for one of your little jokes.
迈克:什么把戏?
Mike: What jokes?
开萝尔:我不知道.可能是一些弱智笑话吧,
Carol: Oh I don't know.
比方说,"
Probably some stupid joke like, "Carol,
开萝尔,
if you really want to improve you looks,
如果你真的想更好看,那为什么不带项链呢"?
why don't you just get a new flea collar?'
迈克:很好,我就喜欢那样,开萝尔.嗨,你自己已经说了.
Mike: That's good.I like that Carol.Hey, you said it.
开萝尔:我只不过把你心里想说的说了出来,如此而已.
Carol: I just beat you to it.That's all.
迈克:对,我觉得我遇到了一两个可以跟我扯平的对手.
Mike: Yeah, I guess I have come up with a zinger or two in my day.
开萝尔:对.
Carol: Yeah.
迈克:等会儿,开萝尔,我开玩笑说你丑跟你今天到这儿做手术有关系,你是这意思么?
Mike: Yeah, kind of like the time I told you to go break a mirror,
or how about the time I told Eddie you were in a bad mood because you
had to be wormed.Wait a minute.
Carol, are you saying that all my little jokes about you being ugly have
something to do with you coming here today?
开萝尔:当然不是.
Carol: Of course not.
迈克:你在撒谎.
Mike: You're lying.
开萝尔:没撒谎.
Carol: I am not.
迈克:撒谎.
Mike: You are.
开萝尔:你以前关于我相貌的话,我会在意么,
Carol: If you think that I am even aware that you have been calling me
我根本都不记得了,如果你还以为我耿耿于怀的话,你简直太可笑了.
funny looking for the past, all my life, you're crazy.
迈克:开萝尔,那你为什么还听我的呢?好了,开萝尔,
Mike: Carol, why would you even listen to me?Come on Carol, look.
你是我的妹妹,我必须老得损你说你丑.那是我的工作.
You're my sister.Alright.I'm supposed to call you ugly.That's my job.
开萝尔:那我现在应该怎么想你?你的意思是你以前只是开玩笑,不是当真,是么?
Carol: What now I suppose you're going to say you didn't mean it?
迈克:好了,好了.
Mike: Look.Ok.Alright, alright.
以前,你骂我超级弱智的时候你都是认真的么?好了,
Look, did you mean it all those times you called me so incredibly stupid?
好了.不是很贴切的例子.
Alright, alright.Bad example.Carol come on now.
开萝尔,不要闹了.这只是哥哥与妹妹的内战.
This is brother and sister stuff here.Look, Eddie calls his sister ugly.
听着,埃德也骂他妹妹丑;鲍纳也觉得自己的妹妹难看.
Boner thinks his sister's ugly.
开萝尔:鲍纳的妹妹的确难看.
Carol: Boners sister is ugly.
迈克:这不是问题所在,开萝尔.
Mike: It's not the point Carol.The point is, you're not ugly.
问题在于,你不难看.说句实话,
As a matter of fact, in the lastcouple of years, you begin kind of...
在过去的几年里,你开始变得有点……你越来越耐看了.
You've been getting better looking.
开萝尔:那当然.
Carol: Oh sure.
迈克:开萝尔,这对我来说很难,
Mike: Carol, this is tough for me alright.
我是以男孩对你的视角来进行观察的,我知道那种容貌意味着什么.
I mean, I see the way guys look at you.I know that look.
开萝尔:是么?
Carol: Yeah?
迈克:对.当你的朋友以那样的目光看你的妹妹的时候,
Mike: Yeah.I mean, you know when your friends look at your sister that way.
你就会明白.有点怪异.
It's kind of weird.
开萝尔:那就是说,你是说……
Carol: So you're saying that...
迈克:(咕咕哝哝)
Mike: (mumbles)
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
迈克:你挺漂亮,我刚才说了我认为你挺漂亮.
Mike: You're pretty.I said I think you are kind of pretty.
开萝尔:你认为我漂亮.
Carol: Well, you think I'm pretty.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.And if you have any kind of sensitivity at all,
如果你还有那么点
you will never ever tell anyone that I said you looked pow wow.Ok?
麦琪:开萝尔,你怎么敢不听我们的话.
Maggie: Carol, how dare you disobey us.
开萝尔:妈妈,爸爸!
Carol: Mum, dad!
杰森:我以前觉得我绝对用不着对你这样,但是现在,
Jason: I never thought I'd hear myself saying this, but Carol Ann Seaver,
开萝尔*安*希佛,你被监禁了.
you are grounded.
开萝尔:等!
Carol: Wait!
麦琪:不用解释了,不会让你做整鼻手术的.
Maggie: No explanations.You are not getting a nose job.
开萝尔:我知道.
Carol: I know.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
开萝尔:我不会做整鼻手术的.
Carol: I'm not getting a nose job.
杰森:不要以为顺着我们说话就可以迷惑住我们.现在,
Jason: Don't confuse us by agreeing with us Carol.
我们回家讨论这个问题.
Now we'll talk about this at home.
麦琪:我们会的,我们得说服你……
Maggie: You bet we will.We have to convince you...
开萝尔:我自己不想做手术,我不需要手术,
Carol: I don't want a nose job.I don't need a nose job.
我这样本来就还可以.事实上,
I look fine just the way I am.
不只是还可以,甚至还可以说是有点漂亮.
In fact I might even be a little bit pretty.
杰森:这事跟你有关系么?
Jason: Did you have anything to do with this?
迈克:我,嗨,我刚才一直劝她去换个脑子.
Mike: Me, hey I was trying to convince her to go for a whole new head.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:好了,我只要确信,你真的认为……
Maggie: Well I just need to know, do you really think...
杰森:对,宝贝,你的鼻子很好看,好看极了.
Jason: Yes honey, your nose is wonderful.It's perfect.
麦琪:谢谢你.你觉得你的鼻子完美么?
Maggie: Thank you.Do you think your nose is perfect?
杰森:当然.
Jason: Sure.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:哪点也看不出来.
Maggie: No reason.
杰森:麦琪,我的鼻子哪儿也没问题,
Jason: Maggie, there's nothing wrong with my nose.OK?
好了吧?坦率地说,我对关于鼻子的讨论有点烦了.
And frankly I'm a little tired with all this nose talk.
麦琪:我同意,亲爱的.
Maggie: I agree sweet heart.
杰森:有点痒,我挠一挠.
麦琪:骗人骗人!
00:22:51,900
Jason: It's itchy.I'm scratching.. Maggie: Honk honk!